Bhaskar Walavi

Sales & Marketing Executive

An organized and creative professional with proven Marketing Skills and a desire to learn more. Possess 4+ years of experience working for a diverse group of organizations and clients. Gained expertise in Field Marketing, Publication Marketing, and Web-Based Advertising. Looking to utilize my existing skill set to increase company profitability.

bhaskarw2015@gmail.com

9403474134

Umaji Nagar, Nashik

.

linkedin.com/in/bhaskar-walavi-43b90117b in

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sales & Marketing ExecutiveVirtuoso Optoelectronics Pvt Ltd.

07/2017 - Present

Nashik

Virtuoso Optoelectronics is a majorly producer of various types of LED Lights and Street Lights.

Tasks

- Meet clients, understand their needs and develop relationships.
- Convince clients about the quality, price and after sales service.
- Provide pre-sales and after-sales technical assistance to client.
- Also having experience in tendering and offer preparations, back office.
- Understands customer requirement and specifications, single line diagram, technical details.
- Having knowledge about Relays, Substation Automation System, Control & Relay Panels, and Substations.

Diploma Trainee

Siemens Ltd.

Tasks

- Worked in Logistic Dept. for 1 year as a Trainee.
- Resolved technical issues between vendors, production and engineering.
- Responsible for order completion on time.

Contract Employee

HAL (Hindustan Aeronautics Ltd)

05/2015 - 06/2016

Nashik

Tasks

 Responsible for Sukhoi-30 Fuel indicators & Transmitters overhauling.

EDUCATION

Diploma in Electrical EngineeringGovernment Polytechnic Nashik

07/2012 - 12/2015

Nashik

SKILLS



ACHIEVEMENTS

Cold-called 20+ potential clients on a daily basis, with a closing rate of 10% to 20%.

Sent 50+ cold emails on a daily basis, managing to set up calls with 10% of the recipients.

Improved product sales by 15%, which led to a 20% increase in annual revenue.

LANGUAGES

Marathi			
English			
Hindi			

INTERESTS

